https://www.quantumdev.com/privacy-policy/

Encoder Store
QM35 Optical Rotary Encoder QML35 Optical Rotary Encoder QM35 EZ-Comm Optical Rotary Encoder
Optical Rotary Encoder Resources
3D Models (log in first) BLDC Motor Commutation Encoder Installation Manuals Encoder Spec Sheets EZ Encoder Facts Line Cards Optical Encoder Basics: What is an Optical Encoder? Photodiode Resources | Photodiode Facts
BlogAboutContact
(608) 924-3000
Log In
Products
Optical Rotary Encoders
OPTOLAB / Line Drivers
Photodiodes
Encoder Store
QM35 Optical Rotary Encoder
QML35 Optical Rotary Encoder
QM35 EZ-Comm Optical Rotary Encoder
Optical Rotary Encoder Resources
3D Models (log in first)
BLDC Motor Commutation
Encoder Installation Manuals
Encoder Spec Sheets
EZ Encoder Facts
Line Cards
Optical Encoder Basics: What is an Optical Encoder?
Photodiode Resources | Photodiode Facts
Blog
About
Contact
Privacy Policy
Quantum Devices, Inc. Privacy Policy
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for Quantum Devices, Inc.  This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Updates
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (608) 924-3000 or via email.
Registration
In order to use portions of this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest.
Orders
We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we’ll use this information to contact you.
Cookies
We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
Sharing
We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes beyond filling your order.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information
Call or Fax
(608) 924-3000
(608) 924-3007
Send a Message
Sales ›
Customer Service ›
Employment Opportunities ›
Employee Portal ›
Password:*
Forgot Password?
Create an account
Create an account to gain access to all of our 3D models!
Create Account
Create Account
Create an account to gain access to all of our 3D models!
First Name:*
Last Name:*
Company:*
Email Address:*
Password:*
Forgot Password
Email Address:*
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.OkPrivacy policy
